Oleg 二号桌的客人问
Oleg, the people at Table Two
蔬菜汉堡里都放了些什么
want to know what's in the veggie burger.
他们不会想知道的
No. They don't.
呃 没关系
Eh. That's fine.
他们想要续杯 所以我大概
They wanted refills, so I'm probably not
不会再去那桌了
gonna go back there anyway.
Max呢?
Where's Max?
这盘菜已经放了很久了
This plate has been here so long,
三文鱼都要变沙门菌了
the salmon is turning into Salmonella.
她和新的洗碗工去休息了
She took a break with the new dishwasher.
Max 我以为你从后门溜出去了
Max, I thought you slipped out the back.
他的确溜出了我的后门 但我把他塞回去了
He did for a minute, but I popped him back in.
我得说 和同事上床之后
This just in, work is so much more fun
工作就变得有趣多了
when you're sleeping with a co-worker.
Max 刚才太爽了
Max, that was good.
和连诵五遍圣母经一样爽
It was five Hail Marys good.
我觉得我们把盘子弄得更脏了
I think we made these dishes dirtier.
Max 他的确可爱 但对着那口音 你怎么硬得起来?
Max, he's cute, but how can you even stay hard with that accent?
"过来 Max 我要和你嘿咻一把"
"Come here, Max. I wanna hump ya a wee bit".
只能说 我一向很喜欢
What can I say, I always had a thing
幸运符麦片盒子上的男孩子
for the guy on the box of Lucky Charms.
破产姐妹花 第四季第18集
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组  http://hdscg.com/ ==--
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调: 。沫   校对: 桃茜茜
翻译: 香锅影  cc  落寞卷菜  morning
大家好
Hey, everybody.
瞧 我买了个运动腕带
Look, I got me a Fitbit.
十三 十四 十五...
13, 14, 15...
再走二十万步 我就能在婚礼上
Only 200,000 more steps before I get a bit more fit
显得苗条一点
for my wedding.
真厉害
That's impressive.
我连十二步都走不了
I couldn't even make it through 12 steps.
嘿 Max
Hey, Max.
我的伴娘今天好吗?
How's my maid of honor?
嘿 Caroline
Hey, Caroline.
我毫不出众的婚礼嘉宾今天好吗?
How's my run-of-the-mill wedding guest?
我很好 你信吗?
I'm doing great. Did that sound convincing?
因为我每天早上都要在浴室镜子前
'Cause I've been practicing it in the bathroom mirror
练习这句话一个小时
for an hour every morning.
我知道 因为你一练习
I know, I've got to stop sitting on the toilet
我就得从马桶上起来
while you do that.
Max 我们商量下伴娘裙的事
Max, let's talk bridesmaid dresses.
我无所谓 穿什么都可以
I don't care, I'll wear anything.
我穿了件灰狗长途车司机的制服去参加的毕业舞会
I wore a Greyhound Bus driver's uniform to my prom.
因为我是下班直接过去的
I was coming straight from work.
我决定穿
Well, I have decided to wear
祖母的结婚礼服
Grandma Kuchenski's wedding gown.
我家所有女人都穿那件出嫁的
Yeah, all of the women in my family wore it.
除了Svetti和Letti阿姨
Everyone except aunts Svetti and Letti,
因为她们是连体儿
'cause, well, they're attached at the abdomen.
你来了
There she is.
让我男式火腿更添味道的宝贝
The hot sauce for my Huevos Mancheros.
嘿 Sophie宝贝 我弄到你想要的东西了
Hey, Sophie, baby, I got you what you want.
Oleg 没人想要肝炎病菌
Oleg, no one wants Hepatitis.
定下了
It's official.
我们的婚礼会被登上纽约时报
Our wedding's gonna be in The Times.
Oleg 你怎么可能上纽约时报?
Oleg, how are you gonna be in The Times?
纽约时报很挑剔的
The Times tends to be picky
而且你只喜欢挖鼻孔
and you tend to be more "picky your nose."
要知道 我的第二次婚礼就上了纽约时报
You know, my second wedding made The Times.
因为我的第一任妻子朝我的腿开了一枪
'Cause my first wife showed up and shot me in the leg.
是我妹妹Vlanka发来的
That's Vlanka, my sister.
她是另一个伴娘
She's my other bridesmaid.
我们的确关系不亲密 但我很同情她
Yeah, we're not that close, but I feel bad for her
因为她长大了 脸上还是有雀斑
'cause she's one of those adults with freckles.
Max 你要上纽约时报了!
Max, you're going to be in The Times!
但得穿Sophie挑的衣服上纽约时报
In The Times, wearing God knows what Sophie will pick.
我是说 她有一抽屉健身时候戴的钻石冠冕
I mean, she has a drawer full of diamond tiaras for the gym.
嘿 你们俩在聊什么?
Hello, what are you two talking about?
决定忽略哪几桌的客人吗?
Deciding which tables to ignore?
我们在说Sophie的品味
We're talking about Sophie's taste.
两位毒舌婊 拜托
Oh, bitch, please. Come on.
我的早餐纤维曲奇都好过Sophie
My morning fiber cookie has better taste than Sophie.
姑娘们 Vlanka下岗了
Girls, Vlanka's out.
她在闹情绪 脸上还有雀斑
She has an attitude and freckles.
我知道 这些八竿子打不着
Yeah. I mean, that's too far.
所以 恭喜Caroline!
So, Caroline, congratulations!
你是我的新伴娘!
You're my new bridesmaid!
好了 我找到条喜欢的伴娘裙
Okay, I found a bridesmaid's dress that I like.
但要想买得起 我只能把你卖给
But the only way we can afford it is if I sell you
分类广告网上的那个亚美尼亚人
to that Armenian guy on Craigslist.
没门
No way.
我最多只能吃四口鹰嘴豆泥
I get sick of hummus after four bites.
Max 我们得掌控局面
Max, we have to take charge of this.
因为无论Sophie挑怎样的伴娘裙
Because whatever bridesmaid's dress Sophie picks
都会像泰勒·派瑞演的电影里的
is like a Tyler Perry movie.
泰勒·派瑞: 美国演员 导演 编剧
我不用看都知道肯定很糟糕
I don't have to see it to know it's gonna be awful.
我们得找些经典漂亮的裙子
We'll find something classy, and beautiful,
然后直接塞给她
and just shove it down her throat.
是谁要给谁塞什么呀?
Who's shoving what down whom?
如果你们没经历 我有哦
And if you don't have a story, I do.
John 我和Max被绑去当伴娘了
John, Max and I got roped into being bridesmaids.
别说了
Stop.
捆绑我喜欢
You had me at rope.
但我不喜欢伴娘
You lost me at bridesmaids.
我去前台站着看礼服了
I'll be at the hostess stand, looking at dresses
然后默默希望有颗小行星
and silently wishing for an asteroid
能把我们从地球上抹去
to wipe us off the planet.
如果希望都能成真 那我们现在
If wishes made things happen, we'd been in the middle
就会被一群僵尸围着了
of a zombie apocalypse right now.
姑娘们好
Hey, girls.
我的礼服从波兰送过来了
My dress just arrived from Poland
我很想让你们看看
and I'm bustin' for you to see it.
你们慢慢看 我在一边吃个十四刀的布丁
See it while I eat one of your $14 puddings.
Sophie 我考虑了一下伴娘服的颜色
Sophie, I've been looking at color choices,
你觉得我们穿裸色的伴娘裙如何?
and how would you feel about us in a nude?
Max裸着还行 可是你没什么好裸的啊
Max could go nude but you don't have the rack to pull it off.
有人有刀吗?
Does anyone have a knife?
Max 你在甜品站工作
Max, why do you have a switchblade
带着把弹簧刀干什么?
to work in a dessert bar?
我妈一直教育我说要做好保护措施
My mother always told me to carry protection.
等着看Kuchenski祖母的婚纱吧
Wait till you see Grandma Kuchenski's dress.
虽然做工也许大不如前了
They don't make them like they used to.
你懂的 现在强迫吉普赛劳工干活是违法的
You know, forced gypsy labor is illegal now.
好了 瞧
Here we go.
- 呕  - 额...
- Oh.  - Uh...
Sophie 你祖母是看守地窖的吗?
Sophie, was your grandma the Crypt Keeper?
这里什么发生了什么?
What's going on out here?
空中飘着这么多白色粉末是什么情况?
What's all that white powder in the air?
我开的是餐厅 不是80年代的迪厅
I'm trying to run a restaurant, not an 80's disco.
哦 闭上你的嘴吧
Oh, put a sock in it.
我可是消费了你那迷之昂贵的糕点的
I'm buying one of your freaking overpriced puddings.
我本该生气 但我现在有点儿喜欢你了
I'd get mad but I'm mildly attracted to you right now.
才一点点?
Just mildly?
老娘这下生气了
I mean, now I'm getting mad.
对不起 都是婚礼惹的祸
Sorry. Wedding drama.
她的婚纱刚刚碎成一片片的...
Her dress just fell completely to pieces...
就像我预想着未来的自己也支离破碎
like I'm assuming I'll do in the near future.
任何跟婚礼有关的东西
Whatever you need bridal,
都能在布鲁克林的那家婚
go to Rosenfeld's in Brooklyn.
在我破产又喜欢男人的时候就在那里买的婚纱
That's where I got my dress when I was broke and straight.
所以说你不是一直喜欢女人的吗?
So you weren't always into women?
我当然一直喜欢的女人
Of course I was.
除了在我信奉科学教的那三年
Except those three years in Scientology.
好吧 看来我们三个
Well, it looks like the three of us
要一起去淘点伴娘裙了
are going to go dress shopping now.
哦 我必须要先去洗个手
Yeah. And you know, I got to go wash my hands
它们上面沾满了老女人的死皮
'cause they're covered in old lady DNA.
好吧 就这样咯
Well, that's that.
和Sophie一起购物 就像是我之前
Shopping with Sophie is like when I worked
在泰式按摩店工作那样
in a Thai massage parlor.
我们要完蛋了
We are going down.
除非我们比Sophie先去那家店
Not if we go before Sophie
把所有她会看上的难看伴娘裙都藏起来
and hide every ugly bridesmaid's dress that Sophie would like.
只要别让她看到 她就不会让咱们穿了
If she can't see them, she can't make us wear them.
你脑子怎么转得这么快?
How did you come up with that so fast?
当我2010年为切尔西·克林顿(前总统克林顿女儿)
It's the same plan I used in 2010
当伴娘的时候用的也是这招
when I was a bridesmaid for Chelsea Clinton.
难看的伴娘裙 然后她爸还尾随我进了更衣室
Bad dress and then her father followed me into the coat room.
哦 哇哦
Oh, wow.
瞧瞧这里
Look at this place.
它让我想起了一部电影
It reminds me of that movie.
- 是"伴娘"吗?  - 不是 是"猛鬼街"
- Bridesmaids?  - No, Nightmare on Elm Street.
Caroline我实在不知道你有什么可担心的
I don't know what you're worried about, Caroline.
我觉得这些婚纱挺漂亮的
I think they're all quite lovely.
Nash 拜托
Nash, please.
你就是一爱尔兰穷小子
You're a poor person from Ireland.
等我想要申请免费的腿支架时
I'll ask your opinion when I need to know where to go
我会向你咨询
to get free leg braces.
你是对的 Max
You were right, Max.
她有时候确实挺贱的
She can be a real "B" sometimes.
抱歉 但我真不知道他为啥也跟着来
I'm sorry, but I don't even know why he's here.
这位山寨版的奥伯里恩
Bonin' O'Brien here...
能够帮我们拖住那些女销售
is gonna distract the sales lady
好让我们去把难看的伴娘裙藏起来
while we hide the ugly dresses.
你们好 女士们
Hello, ladies.
计划不变
Same plan.
哪位是幸运的新娘?
Who's the lucky bride?
或许我该说 哪位有幸地吃到小鲜肉了?
Or should I say, who's the lucky cradle robber?
别管我
Don't mind me.
我的幽默感太澎湃了
It's just my crazy sense of humor.
这里的女士们都爱死我的幽默感
Oh, the ladies here love it.
她们管我叫"狂野Carl"
The call me "Crazy Carl."
"你刚听到狂野Carl说什么了吗?"
"Did you hear what Crazy Carl said?"
她们就是爱死我了
They just love it.
我是Caroline
I'm Caroline.
这是Max 而他不是新郎
This is Max and he isn't the groom.
没错
No, no, no.
他是一个单身同性恋
He's single and gay. Yes.
太弯了 以至于他被单向组合乐队给踢了出来
So gay, he got kicked out of One Direction.
你们俩何不出去走走
Why don't you two walk off somewhere
聊聊辛酸的出柜史呢
and share poignant coming-out stories.
快去
Go.
- 但是Max...  - 哦 听话 快去吧
- But Max...  - Oh, you heard the women, go.
倒也可以
Can do.
女士们 你们随便看看 我们...
Ladies, look around, we'll be back...
一个月后回来
in about a month.
有人想去大溪地度假吗
Tahiti anyone?
我就是如此疯狂的Carl
I'm just Crazy Carl.
女士们爱死我了
The ladies love it.
好的伴娘服就该有伴娘服的样子
Bridesmaid's dresses should be called what they are.
捐给慈善机构的昂贵捐赠啊
Really expensive donations to Goodwill.
这件丑吗?
Is this one bad?
开玩笑 这件可是国际名牌
No. That's a Vera Wang.
但是这件 绝对不行
But this is a very wrong.
藏起来
Hide it.
咦 还有一个一样丑的姐妹装
Ew. And it's evil twin.
哦 居然还有带着羽毛的救生衣
Oh, I didn't know Hazmat suits came with feathers.
天啊
Oh my God.
这是我见过的最可怕的东西了
This the worst thing I've ever seen.
我甚至见过一个妓女在人行道上
And I've seen a prostitute change her tampon
换卫生棉
on the sidewalk.
你叫谁妓女呢?
Who are you calling a prostitute?
快 我们一定得把这件藏起来
This, we've got to hide.
我脱不下来
I can't get this dress off.
只要跟她说 你在谷歌工作
Just tell it you work at Google
而且你想定居下来 就会有人帮你脱衣服了
and you're thinking of settling down.
抬起来 抬起来啊 把她丢进去
Lift it up. Lift it up. Dump it back there.
住手!
Stop!
把可爱的黄油贝蒂放下来
You put Butterscotch Betty down.
哦 我们只是在找价格标签
Oh, we were just looking for a price tag.
我知道你们在干什么
I know what's going on here.
你们想把漂亮衣服藏起来
You're hiding the good dresses
让别人找不到 好等到我们明天
to make sure no one else can get them
年度半价活动之时来抢购
at our annual half-off sale tomorrow.
没错 我们就是这么打算的
Yeah, that's what we're doing.
我们要把漂亮衣服藏起来
We're hiding the good dresses.
其实 我刚还抓到另一个人也是这样
In fact, I just caught another Sneaky Sue.
哦 就是我 Sophie
Oh, I'm Sophie.
哦 哇 哇 哇
Oh, wow, wow, wow.
哦 看看这个颜色
Oh, look at the color.
那不是颜色 那是辐射
That's not color. That's radiation.
这件裙子是独一无二的
That dress is a one of a kind.
就是说 只有一件?
Meaning there's only one?
不 我们有两件
No, we have two.
我正好有两个伴娘!
And I have two bridesmaids!
生活如此完美 我真是太开心了
I love it when life works out perfect like this.
看看这个地方吧
Look at this place.
这么多绝望的女人挤在这
There are more desperate women crammed in here
比肯尼·切斯尼演唱会飞溅区的人还要多
than the splash zone at a Kenny Chesney concert.
没错 就跟沃尔玛的黑色星期五一样
I know. It's like Black Friday at Walmart
我宁肯在踩踏事件中丧生
And like Black Friday, hopefully someone will trample me.
多亏了那些裙子 我的人生就这么完蛋了
Cause thanks to these dresses, my life is over.
Max 你在听我说话吗?
Max, did you hear me?
我的人生完蛋了
My life is over.
那次中国餐厅忘了给你鸭酱
You said that when the Chinese food place
你就是这么说的
forgot the duck sauce.
好吧 对不起 我只是想以一个全新的形象
Well, I'm sorry, but I had a whole other scenario planned
重返时代杂志
for my return to The Times.
"重振旗鼓的女强人"
"Entrepreneur rises from the ashes."
可现在 我只能像小丑一样
Now, I'm just going to be in The Times,
出现在杂志里
looking like a stupid ash.
往前挤啊 大姐 给点力啊
Shoot, girl, just push on through.
我正在挤呢 我在挤啊
I'm pushing, girl. I am pushing.
借过
Excuse us.
往前走啊 大姐
Just go, girl.
我可不想别人把那两件
I don't want anybody else to get those
黄色裙子抢走
two yellow dresses.
Max 你听见了吗?
Max, did you hear that?
有人比Sophie的品味还差
Someone has worst taste than Sophie.
我们躲到她们后面去
Now we just have to hang back here
让她们先把裙子买了
and let them get to those dresses first.
耶! 我的人生又重见天日了
Yay! My life is good again.
Max Caroline 这里
Max, Caroline, up here.
什么 只让我开心一秒吗?
What was that, like, a second?
我给你们占位子了
I saved you a space upfront.
快过来
Come on.
好吧 看来没希望了
Well, it's over.
一旦他们剪下缎带 开始营业
As soon as they cut that ribbon,
Sophie就要把任何挡在我们和
Sophie's going to Marshawn Lynch everyone who
黄色裙子中间的人给撂倒了
gets in the way of us and those dresses.
只有一个办法
There's only one way out of this.
就是你刚才提到的
And you called it earlier.
你得制造一起踩踏事件
You have to let them trample you.
我是认真的
I'm serious.
我才不要故意摔倒被人踩呢
I'm not about to be trampled on purpose.
如果听见下面这些话
See if you still feel that way
你会做何感想
after I say these next few words:
"图中左一 Caroline Channing"
"Pictured from left, Caroline Channing."
把那些试图往我眼睛上踩的高跟鞋推开
Try to fend off any heels you see heading for my eyes.
注意了 女士们
Attention, ladies.
如你们所见 我手上有一把大剪刀
As you see, I have the big scissors,
也就意味着 是时候...
which can only mean it's time...
剪鼻毛啦!
to trim some nose hairs!
真是疯狂的Carl
That Carl is crazy.
年度婚纱特价销售活动...
The annual bridal sale...
- 现在...  - Max 抓住我的手
- is now...  - Max, hold my hand.
开幕!
Open!
女士们 女士们 一次一件
Ladies, ladies, one at a time.
哦!
Oh!
虽然我是蹒跚着走完过道的
Well, I may be limping down the aisle,
但至少我不是在速易洁清洁公司卖的
but at least I won't be limping in something Swiffer might sell
吊扇除尘器下走过
to dust off ceiling fans.
天啊! 她来了!
Oh, my God, girl! here she comes!
她来了
Here she comes.
我朋友Rhonda 她先拿到裙子的
My girl, Rhonda, had that dress first.
哦 你们必须
Oh, your girl is gonna have to
从我冰冷的死亡之手里把它撬出来
pry it out of my cold, dead hands.
嘿 Max Caroline!
Hey, Max, Caroline!
试穿它! 试穿它!
Try it on! Try it on!
请跟我来更衣室
Follow me to the changing room.
我不要穿着这条裙子出去 我害怕
I'm never coming out in this dress, I'm scared.
我数 一 二...
So on the count of one, two...
也许没那么糟
Maybe it's not that bad.
很糟
It's bad.
好吧 告诉我
Okay. So you're telling me,
范哲思被杀了
Versace got murdered,
范哲思，1978年创立Versace奢侈品牌，1998年被黑社会谋杀
却没有人把设计这衣服的人杀了?
but no one's taken out whoever made these?
我懂
I know.
我感觉翠迪鸟要起诉我们
I feel like Tweety Bird is gonna sue us
黄色小鸟的卡通形象，由华纳出品
侵权了啊
for copyright infringement.
我感觉我们应该在下面放巨型的厕所卷纸
I feel like we should have giant toilet paper rolls under here.
也许没有这强光之后
Well, maybe we'll like these better
我们会更喜欢这衣服
when we're out of this bright light.
Max 这强光就是我们自己
Max, we are the bright light.
女士们 你们把配套的帽子给忘了
Ladies, you forgot the matching hats.
还有吗?
There's more?
对了 要是有人发现一片赞安诺 那是我的
Oh, if anyone finds a Xanax, it's mine.
赞安诺一般用于治疗焦虑和失眠
两个女人争夺一条印花鱼尾裙时
It was knocked out of my hand by two women duking it out
药片在我手里被撞掉了
over a chintz mermaid dress.
哦 现在好看了
Oh, now it looks good.
赞安诺在外逍遥 我却站在这里?
There's Xanax on the loose and I'm just standing here?
除了我磕高了 我才有理由穿这种衣服
At least if I was high, I'd have an excuse to be wearing this.
药啊 药啊 到这儿来
Here pilly, pilly.
Here pilly, pilly, pilly.
妹子 说真的 你们穿上这裙子
Girl, for real, you look like straight up crap
真是烂透了
in that dress.
真的
For real.
你们白人女孩撑不起这种颜色
You white girls can't pull that color off.
真是浪费了耀眼的柠檬黄
That's a waste of poppin' lemon yellow.
我知道
I know.
我太白了 不能穿这个
I am way too white for this.
她也因为太白了而无法一直学黑人说"畅饮"
She's also too white to say "turnt up" all the time,
但她还是会说
but that hasn't stopped her.
这条裙子不是我选的
This dress was not my choice.
我一点也不喜欢它
I hate everything about it.
这就是个灾难
This is a disaster.
这就是"末日裙子"
This is "Dressageddon."
对 但这是褒义
Yeah, but in a good way.
你们俩不想穿这条裙子
You two don't want to wear the dresses.
你们不一定要穿
You don't have to.
可我以为你想要我们
But I thought you wanted us to match
跟气球和鸭子搭配
the balloons and the ducks.
Max 她说我们不必穿这裙子
Max, she said we don't have to wear the dress.
别质疑她!
Don't question her!
就像在监狱的守卫说你可以走了时
That's like questioning a prison guard
你却在质疑他一样
when he says you're free to go.
Sophie 你确定你不介意吗?
Sophie, are you sure you don't care?
是啊 当然
Oh, yeah. Sure.
裙子是你们的了 命运的宠儿
Yeah, they're all yours, Destiny's Child.
这丑陋的垃圾货有十磅重
This is ten pounds of ugly junk.
让我想起我曾经约会过的酒保Pete
Reminds me of this bartender, Pete, I used to date.
仔细想想 那也把我噎住了
Come to think of it, that made me gag, too.
好了 搞定
Okay. Done.
你听 女更衣室里有哭声?
Listen, crying in a women's dressing room?
不管你是谁 姑娘 知心大妈来了
Whoever it is, girl, big butts are in.
那是Sophie的哭声
That's Sophie's cry.
我知道 是因为她在看"下一站歌后"时
I know, 'cause I hear it through the vent
我从通风口听到过
when she watches Nashville.
Sophie 是你吗?
Sophie?
不是
No.
你还好吗?
Are you okay?
不是我 但我没事
It's not me, but I'm okay.
Sophie 你为什么哭?
Sophie, why are you crying?
我听到你们对那裙子的评论时...
When I heard what you said about the dresses...
只是...
It's just...
就是 有点像是
It's almost, kind of like,
你们觉得我品味很差之类的
you think I have bad taste or something.
不
No.
Caroline觉得你品味很棒
Caroline thinks you have great taste.
是吗?
She does?
那她就应该这样说啊
Well, then she should say so.
马上
Now.
Sophie 我觉得你有自己独特的风格
Well, Sophie, I think you have your own unique style.
我觉得...
And I think...
我没有听见"很好"或者"品味"这些词
that I didn't hear the words "great" or "taste."
Sophie 你介意我的想法干嘛?
Sophie, what do you even care what I think?
你就直说吧!
Just say it!
Sophie 我觉得你品味很好
Sophie, I think you have great taste.
真的吗?
You do?
那我们还坐在这儿干嘛?
Then, what are we doing sitting here?
我们去把裙子拿回来!
Let's go and get those dresses back!
快 帮我!
Come on. Help me!
裙子已经被别的姑娘拿走了
Those other girls already took them.
什么?
What?
至少我们不用再婚礼上穿着
Well, at least we don't have to wear those ugly,
那些难看的黄色伴娘裙了
yellow bridesmaid dresses at the wedding.
是啊 现在 你只需要
Yup. Now, you only have to wear
每晚在这里穿难看的黄色裙子
ugly, yellow dresses here, every night.
自从我意识到我手臂上的怪痣
This is the best thing that's happened to me
是葡萄果仁麦片 而不是癌症
since I realized that weird mole on my arm was just a Grape-Nut
这是我遇到最好的事了
and not cancer.
姑娘们 好消息
Girls, great news.
你们把Han塞进了微波炉
You stuffed Han in the microwave
现在准备插电了吗?
and you're ready to hit power?
拜托 我们试过了
Come on. We've tried.
你知道他进不去的
You know he doesn't fit.
这是唯一让他显得体积太大的东西
The one thing he's too big for.
不 我请了Ilia Jorbich来当我们的婚礼摄影师
No, I got Ilia Jorbich to be our wedding photographer.
他是华沙时报最好的摄影师
He's the best photographer at The Warsaw Times.
也是唯一还有两条手臂的人
Well, he's the only one who still has both arms.
等等 是华沙时报吗?
Wait, it's the Warsaw Times?
这么久以来 我一直以为是
All this time, I've been thinking
纽约时报
it was The New York Times.
纽约时报?
New York Times?
我这个更加独家好吗
This is much more exclusive.
你只能在两个地方找到它
You can only get it in two places.
波兰以及新泽西州卖导弹的熟食店
Poland and the deli in New Jersey that sells missiles.
太不可思议了
This is amazing.
我在纽约时报的复出
My comeback in The New York Times
被保存下来了
has been preserved.
Max 我要微笑着继续前进
Max, I'm gonna go ahead and smile.
我的生活又美好了
My life is good again.
先别笑 因为Sophie跟我说
Don't smile yet, 'cause Sophie told me
因为你说她品味很好
that because you said she had such good taste,
她正亲自设计我们的裙子
she's designing our dresses herself.
什么 只能开心一秒钟?
What was that, like a second?
是的 你刚刚从最好的时报
Yup. You just went from the best of times
走到了华沙时报
to The Warsaw Times.